<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">HockeyApp</string>
    <string name="team_first">Buffalo Sabers</string>
    <string name="team_second">Washington Capitals</string>
    <string name="score_second">2</string>
    <string name="score_first">1</string>
    <string name="two_point">:</string>
    <string name="october_25">October, 25</string>
    <string name="games">Games</string>
    <string name="teams">Teams</string>


    <string name="team_coachella">Coachella Valley Firebirds</string>
    <string name="team_bears">Hershey Bears</string>
    <string name="team_milwaukee">Milwaukee Admirals</string>
    <string name="team_rochester">Rochester Americans</string>
    <string name="team_texas">Texas Stars</string>
    <string name="team_calgary">Calgary Wranglers</string>
    <string name="team_toronto">Toronto Marlies</string>
    <string name="team_hartford">Hartford Wolf Pack</string>
    <string name="team_manitoba">Manitoba Moose</string>

    <string name="score_one">2 : 3</string>
    <string name="score_two">1 : 0</string>
    <string name="score_three">4 : 3</string>
    <string name="score_four">0 : 1</string>
    <string name="score_five">5 : 3</string>
    <string name="score_six">2 : 3</string>
    <string name="score_seven">6 : 5</string>
    <string name="score_eight">8 : 4</string>
    <string name="score_nine">1 : 3</string>
    <string name="score_ten">2 : 1</string>


    <string name="hockey_ring">Near each end of the rink there is a red goal line spanning the width of the ice. It is used to judge goals and icing calls.\n
        \nNew since the 2005–06 NHL season, after testing in the American Hockey League, a trapezoid is marked behind each goalie net. The goalie can only play the puck within that area or in front of the goal line. If he plays the puck behind the goal line and not in the trapezoid, a 2-minute minor penalty for delay of game will be assessed by the referees. This rule is widely referred to as the "Brodeur rule", after New Jersey Devils goalie Martin Brodeur, whose puckhandling behind the net is believed to be the cause for the rule. In 2014, the NHL lengthened the goal-line side of the trapezoid by two feet on both sides of the net.</string>
    <string name="game_timing">In the National Hockey League, between stoppages of play, teams have 18 seconds (five seconds for the visiting team, eight seconds for the home team, five seconds to line up at the faceoff location) to substitute their players, except during TV timeouts. TV timeouts are two minutes long, and occur three times per period, during normal game stoppages after the 6, 10, and 14 minute marks of the period, unless there is a power play, a goal that has just been scored, or the stoppage was as a result of an icing. Each team may also take one 30 second time-out, but it may only be taken during a normal stoppage of play. Each period, teams rotate nets, therefore changing attacking directions.</string>
    <string name="scoring" tools:ignore="TypographyOther">A goal is scored when the puck passes entirely across the red line painted between the goal posts and below the crossbar.\n
        \nA goal may be disallowed under the following circumstances:\n
        \n1) The scoring team takes a penalty (except if the other team puts the puck into its own net untouched by the team to be penalized)\n
        \n2) The puck is directed in by an attacker high stick (above the crossbar)\n
        \n3) The puck has been directed, batted, thrown or kicked into the net by an attacking player other than with a stick (angling one\'s skate so the puck deflects off it into the goal is allowed)\n
        \n4) Goaltender interference (which can also result in a penalty)\n
        \n5) The puck goes in after a referee intends to stop play (e.g. the net has been dislodged)\n
        \n6) The puck deflects off a referee or linesman and goes directly into the goal (exception to the rule that a puck hitting a referee or a linesman is still live)\n
        \n7) A goal was allowed at the other end (this can happen if a video review clarifies a goal scored prior, as happened in a game on November 15, 2010, between the Los Angeles Kings and San Jose Sharks)\n
        \n8) If a linesman reports to the referee (a) a double-minor for high-sticking, (b) a major penalty, or (c) a match penalty against the scoring team.\n
        \nWhen a regular-season game is tied at the end of regulation, it goes into a three-on-three, five-minute overtime period after a one-minute rest period with teams reversing the attacking direction. If a goal is scored during this period, the game ends and the team that scored the goal wins the game. If there is no scoring in the five-minute overtime, the game goes into a three-round shootout with the home team given the choice of shooting or defending first. This sequence ends when one team mathematically has more shootout goals than the other, thus winning the game. If neither team emerges victorious, the shootout continues one frame at a time until one team scores and the other does not, in which case the team that scores is given the win. A team that loses a game in overtime or the shootout receives one point in the standings; the awarding of game points to losing teams is a point of debate among fans and the media.</string>
    <string name="offside">In ice hockey, play is said to be offside if a player on the attacking
        team crosses the offensive blue line and into the offensive zone before the puck (unless
        the defensive team brings the puck into their own zone). A violation occurs when an offside
        player touches the puck. If a player crosses the line ahead of the puck but his team is not
        in possession of it, the linesman will raise his arm to signal a delayed offside; when all
        players from the offside team leave their offensive zone ("tag up" in the neutral zone) the
        linesman washes out the delayed call. When an offside violation occurs, the linesman blows
        the play dead, and a faceoff is conducted in the neutral zone. During the 2004–05 lockout,
        the league removed the "two-line offside pass" rule, which required a stoppage in play if a
        pass originating from inside a team is defending zone was completed on the offensive side of
        the center line, unless the puck crossed the line before the player.
        The removal of the two-line offside was one of several rule changes intended to increase
        overall scoring, which had been in decline since the early 1990s. The only time a player
        may precede the puck into the attacking zone with the puck behind in the neutral zone is
        if none of his teammates are in the attacking zone and the player with the puck has control
        of the puck in the estimation of the linesman (e.g. short-sticking/spin-o-rama).</string>
    <string name="icing">Icing occurs when a player shoots the puck across both the center line and
        the opposing team is goal line without the puck going through the goal crease. When icing
        occurs, a linesman stops play if a defending player (other than the goaltender) crosses the
        imaginary line that connects the two faceoff dots in their defensive zone before an
        attacking player is able to. If the attacking player beats the defender for the puck, the
        icing is waved off. Play is resumed with a faceoff in the defending zone of the team that
        committed the infraction. Icing is not enforced for a team that is short-handed. If the
        goaltender makes a move from his net to play the puck, the icing is immediately waved off
        (in contrast to minor league and international hockey, where the goaltender must play the
        puck for it to be waved off). Icing can also be waved off if, in the officials opinion, the
        defending team had a viable opportunity to play the puck before crossing the goal line.
        After an icing, a TV timeout cannot be called. The team who iced the puck may not make any
        line changes before the following faceoff.</string>
    <string name="face_offs">Face-offs are used to start play at the beginning of each period and
        after all stoppages of play. At all levels of play, the teams line up in opposition to one
        another, and one player from each team (normally the centre) face each other at a
        designated point on the ice. Once a game official drops the puck between the two opposing
        skaters sticks, they attempt to gain control of it.\n
        \nThe face-off procedure differs slightly between NHL and international rules. Prior to
        the 2015–16 NHL season, the away team is centre was required to place his stick on the ice
        first. Since that season, this is true only for face-offs on the centre-line dot; for
        face-offs in either attacking zone, the defending centre must place his stick first.
        Under international rules, the attacking centre must place his stick first for all
        face-offs.</string>
    <string name="eligibility">The Trushinski bylaw says players who are blind in one or both eyes
        are ineligible to play. The rule is named for Frank Trushinski, a minor league hockey
        player for the Kitchener Greenshirts. Trushinski lost his sight in one eye in a game in
        1921, but was allowed to continue playing. In a later game, he suffered a skull fracture
        which cost him most of the sight in his other eye.</string>
    <string name="helmets">In August 1979, John Ziegler Jr., the president of the National Hockey
        League, announced that protective helmets would become mandatory in the NHL. "The
        introduction of the helmet rule will be an additional safety factor", he said. The only
        exception to the rule are players—after signing a waiver form—who signed pro contracts
        prior to June 1, 1979. Essentially, this grandfather clause allowed hockey is veterans to
        choose whether or not they wanted to wear helmets but forced all new players to wear them.\n
        \nIn 2013, visors in helmets became mandatory for players with 25 or less games of NHL
        experience. However, players who wore helmets without visors prior to the rule change may
        continue to wear them.\n
        \nBeginning the 2019–20 NHL season, a player on the ice whose helmet comes off must either
        pick it up and put it on properly, or skate to the bench (with a reasonable opportunity to
        complete his immediate play). Otherwise, a minor penalty shall be assessed. Intentionally
        removing an opponent is helmet during play became a roughing offense punishable with a minor
        penalty.</string>
    <string name="penalties">A penalty is a punishment for infractions of the rules. A referee
        makes most penalty calls while the linesmen may call only obvious technical infractions
        such as too many men on the ice. In the NHL, the linesmen may also stop play due to player
        injury, and may report to the referees, during any stoppage in play, any circumstances
        pertaining to major, match, or misconduct penalties, abuse of officials (physical or
        otherwise), unsportsmanlike conduct, or double-minor penalties for high-sticking causing
        injury, that were not detected by the referees.\n
        \nDuring a penalty, the player who committed the infraction is sent to the penalty box.
        Small infractions are deemed minor penalties, and the player is kept off the ice for two
        minutes of gameplay. A larger infraction such as high-sticking that causes the victimized
        player to have a visible physical injury is deemed a double-minor, and the perpetrator is
        kept off the ice for four minutes. More dangerous infractions, such as fighting, are deemed
        major penalties and have a duration of five minutes. The penalized team cannot replace the
        player on the ice and is thus short-handed for the duration of the penalty. Normally,
        hockey teams have five skaters (plus the goaltender) on the ice. If a minor or major
        penalty is called, play becomes "five-on-four"—five skaters versus four skaters. This
        situation is called a power play for the non-penalized team and a penalty kill for the
        penalized team; a team is far more likely to score on a power play than during normal play.
        If the penalized team is scored on during a minor penalty, the penalty immediately
        terminates. A double-minor is divided into two separate two-minute minor penalties that are
        served consecutively. This means that if a goal is scored by the team on the power play
        before the first minor is over (before the two-minute mark of the power play), the first
        minor ends and the penalty clock goes down to two minutes. If a goal is scored during the
        second minor (after the two-minute mark of the power play), the penalty ends. Unlike minor
        penalties, major penalties must be served to their full completion, regardless of number
        of goals scored during the power play.\n
        \nWhen a penalty is about to be called, an official will raise his arm to signal what is
        referred to as a "delayed penalty"; play will continue until the offending team touches the
        puck, at which point, the official will blow the play dead and assess the penalty. After a
        penalty is assessed, play resumes with a face-off in the offending team is defensive zone
        under most circumstances. If a delayed penalty is called and goes to the end of the period
        then the full penalty goes to the next period. If a penalty is called with less than two
        minutes to go in a period, except for overtime, a penalty is "carried over" into the next
        period, meaning that any power plays called in the final two minutes of a period move along
        to the next period, meaning that if a penalty is called at 19:01 in the first period, then
        the remaining 1:01 of the power play will go to the second period.\n
        \nIf the team committing a penalty yields a goal and is already short-handed because of a
        minor penalty, the penalty will be called when the goal is scored, and the team scoring a
        goal will be awarded a fresh power play. Furthermore, when goals are scored, penalties come
        off the board in the order in which they were called (if multiple penalties have been
        called). If a goaltender takes a penalty (etc. delay of game), a player who was on the ice
        at the time of the penalty goes to the penalty box, and the goalie stays in game.</string>
    <string name="team_roster">The maximum number of players on an NHL roster is 20. A team can
        have a maximum of 50 signed players and a total of 90 players (unsigned and signed).</string>
    <string name="potential_rule_changes">In August 2010, the NHL held an "R &amp; D camp" at the
        Toronto Maple Leafs practice facility, where rule changes under consideration were given
        trial runs. Scrimmages at the camp, featuring some top players eligible for the 2011 NHL
        Entry Draft, experimented with changes such as two-on-two overtime, shallower goal nets,
        a referee viewing the play from an elevated off-ice platform, and a rink with three
        face-off circles instead of the traditional five.</string>

</resources>